[roars]
[narrator]
Strange beasts
and monsters.
Vast riches.
Hidden treasures.
Evil haunts.
Uncharted frontiers.
The mysterious unknown.
The people who are captivated
by the magic in those words...
are called...
Hunters.
FREECSS
THEN X AND X AFTER
[Mito Freecss]
"Dear Aunt Mito and Grandma, how are you?
I'm doing great, as usual.
The Hunter Exam is finally over now
and turns out, I actually passed!"
[Grandma heaves]
"But while I passed and everything,
I can't say
that I'm all that happy about it,
[Gon Freecss] Because of what happened
in the Final Phase."
[Hanzo] I see you're not getting it,
so I'll try again.
Die and you'll never get
another chance.
If I kill you right here and now,
I only need to come back
and take the Exam again next year.
[raising his voice]
We are not on equal footing!
[yelling] Is your pride
truly all that you care about?
Even more than your life?
Is it worth dying for?
I'm gonna go see my dad.
[surprised gasping]
See, my dad is a Hunter.
So I'm gonna become a Hunter
exactly like he is
and then I'll be able to meet him.
I know I'll find him someday.
But I feel like if I surrender now
I'm never gonna find him.
So, I won't give up.
Surrender...
or you will die.
[Hanzo]
So logic had nothing to do with it.
Fine, you win. I give up, okay?
No fair!
We both have to come up with
some way that we can have a proper match.
[screaming]
Moron!
[Gon]
"I kind of got knocked out.
So, I don't really remember anything
after that.
but Mr. Satotz told me
what happened next."
Begin!
It's been awhile, Kil.
[chirring]
[fearful gasping]
Big brother...
You're not cut out to be a Hunter.
You were born for one purpose...
to be an assassin.
What do you imagine that
you would accomplish by becoming a Hunter?
[Killua Zoldyck]
It's true.
I don't really want to be a Hunter.
But...
Everyone wants something...
Even me.
-You don't.
-Wrong!
There is something that I really want!
[Illumi Zoldyck]
Hm.
Enlighten me.
What is it that you want?
I... want to be...
friends with Gon.
I... I'm just so sick of killing people.
I want to be friends with Gon
and just have fun.
Impossible.
You are incapable of friendship,
because you are by nature
a murderer.
Move one more inch,
and I'll assume the fight has begun.
The same goes...
for if our bodies come in contact
with each other.
The fight starts.
If you decide that you won't fight me,
your dear Gon will certainly die.
[Killua breathes uneasily]
You win, Illumi.
I admit defeat.
[Gon] "I think that's when
Killua hit rock bottom."
[blasting sound]
Apologize to Killua!
Sorry.
But what for?
You don't know what you did wrong?
[gasping]
Don't even bother apologizing.
Just take me to see Killua.
And what will you do?
It's obvious.
I'll bring him back.
[Gon]
"And after that, Kurapika, Leorio and I
made our way to Kukuroo Mountain.
That's where Killua lives."
This gate is officially known as
the Testing Gate.
Because anyone who's not strong enough
to open it...
[huffs]
...is considered unworthy of entering
the Zoldyck Estate.
[groans]
Listen to me, Gon.
You three can try
to open the door together.
There's nothing wrong with teamwork.
And with a little bit of training,
it should be possible.
[shouting]
[Leorio Paradinight]
Let's do this, Kurapika!
Well, let's push!
Here goes!
Ready!
Get set!
Go!
[straining]
[Gon] Ow!
[panting]
It opened.
[Leorio]
Hell yeah!
[Kurapika]
We really did it, Gon!
[Gon]
Uh-huh!
Please leave now.
You're trespassing on private property.
I can't allow you
to pass without permission.
Take one step past it,
and I'll remove you by force if necessary.
[booming]
[Gon]
What's the big deal?
I just came here to see my friend.
[loudly] The only reason I'm here
is to see Killua.
[yelling] So why are you making me
go through all of this?
[cawing]
I can tell you're different from Mike.
You may be trying
to cover up your feelings,
but you still have a heart.
When I mentioned Killua's name
your eyes softened...
just for a moment.
[shaky breathing]
[Canary]
Please...
Help him...
Help Master Ki--
[bursting noise]
[gasping]
And you must be Gon.
Illumi told me all about you.
Killua is aware that you've been
on the premises for some time now.
Why can't Killua come to see us?
Where is he?
In solitary confinement.
Wait, what?
And then,
because he regretted what he had done,
our Killua returned to us.
And entered
solitary confinement voluntarily.
I will take you to the butler's quarters.
There is a phone
that connects directly to the mansion.
If Master Zeno answers it,
he might...
So, which hand?
I've known Master Killua
his entire life.
And I care for him as I would my own son.
In all honesty,
I despise you
for attempting to take him away.
If you answer incorrectly, you are out.
Should you all be disqualified,
which is quite possible, then I shall tell
Master Killua that you left.
And that he will never see
any of you again.
-Here we go.
-Wait just a minute!
What is it?
If you're trying to buy time,
I will kill one of you.
[grunts]
[Kurapika]
He cut himself to reduce the swelling.
There, much better.
I can see now.
Okay, I'm ready.
[gasping]
Now, which one of us has it?
That guy, right behind me.
Splendid, well done.
Gotoh, is Gon here yet?
-Killua!
-You're already here, Gon!
And this guy, uh... Kurapika?
You remembered.
Riolio!
[yelling]
It's Leorio!
It's been so long.
But you made it!
Ha.
Your face is a mess!
Back at ya!
[laughing]
[Gon]
"And just like that,
we managed to rescue Killua.
I know that I should be happy right now,
but I still have some unfinished business
that I need to take care of, Aunt Mito."
HUNTER GLOSSARY
A B C D E F G H I J K L M N
O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z
[Gon]
"I need to take care of something
that happened
in the Fourth Phase of the Exam."
To begin with, I will need each of you
to draw lots, now.
-[all gasp]
-Really?
Draw lots for what?
What'll that decide?
Hm, who you hunt and who hunts you.
Listen carefully!
Collecting the ID badge of
your specified target
will earn you three points,
understand?
Your own badge is also worth
three points.
And all the other badges
are worth one point.
In order to move on to the Final Phase,
you'll have to collect six points.
So during your time there
on Zevil Island,
gather enough badges to collect six points
or fail the Exam.
Only those who do will clear
the Fourth Phase of the Hunter Exam.
So, uh... who did you get?
You want to show our numbers
at the same time?
Okay.
[both]
Ready, and...!
[gasping]
[Killua] Number 44 is...
[Gon] Really?
If I had to fight with Hisoka one-on-one
I wouldn't stand a chance against him.
But if all I have to do
is just steal his badge,
I don't know...
I think I might actually have a real shot.
Yeah.
The way it is now, well,
at least I've got a chance.
And to be honest,
it does scare me a little bit.
But I think it's worth it.
Now!
I did it!
I figured it out!
I've just got to go for the target
the moment it goes for its prey!
There!
I've only got about a minute or so
before Hisoka spots him.
I need to figure out where
their paths are going to cross.
Got it!
I’ve got to hurry.
Hisoka will attack
the second he notices that guy.
If I want to steal his badge,
this is it.
It's the last chance I'm going to get.
I have to stay hidden.
I can't let him sense me.
Focus.
[booming]
[Gon]
Here he comes.
[Agon]
Hisoka!
Damn it, bring it on!
[screams]
[Gon] I did it.
I took Hisoka's badge from him.
[groans]
[Geretta]
About 7000.
Do you even know
what that number represents?
That is the number of chances I had
to kill you.
[whimpers]
It's also
about the number of times that you cast
your fishing rod
while you were training.
In the future,
remember to watch your back.
So long.
[Gon]
Damn it.
[gasps]
You surprise me.
You hid your presence from me
while you were waiting
for your chance to strike.
Biding your time until the very moment
that I attacked someone else.
Did you learn how to conceal yourself
all on your own?
Marvelous.
You're like a wild animal.
And your timing was just impeccable.
You were able to conceal
your blood lust
by cleverly hiding it behind mine
so that I wouldn't notice.
Masterfully done.
[Gon]
Wait.
[straining to speak]
If you're not taking your badge,
then why are you here?
To say congratulations!
You owe me one now.
You can pay me back
whenever you like.
So long.
I don't owe you or anybody.
Here, take it back.
[laughs]
I refuse.
I've decided to let you live,
for now.
And I plan to let you continue living
for as long as it suits me.
Until someday you become
truly worthy of killing.
[booming]
I will take it back.
But only when you can punch me
in the face like that.
In the meantime,
you just hold onto it for me.
[Hisoka laughs]
[Gon] "It was the first time
I've ever felt that frustrated.
That's why I need to find a way
to pay Hisoka back.
I don't want to come back to Whale Island
feeling like I do.
[Mito] That's why I'll be going to
Heaven's Arena with Killua.
It's time for me to start my training
as a Hunter.
So please take care of yourselves.
I can't wait to see you both
when I get back.
Gon Freecss."
I didn't expect him home anytime soon.
He really is your son, isn't he?
[laughs]
Wherever you are,
I hope you're watching over him,
Ging.
[Gon] Next time,
"Arrival x at x the Arena."
Off we go!
Gon, Gon!
[Killua]
What, again?